Caryn Behnke

Manager, Portillos

Minooka, IL 60447 behnke.ca@gmail.com +1 815 685 9995

Results-focused management professional offering 10+ years of progressive leadership experience. Transforming high-potential staff into outstanding leaders who demonstrate the creativity and savvy that is critical to financial and operational success. Looking for a fast paced environment and a company to expand my knowledge and grow with.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Manager

Portillo's Hot Dogs, Chicago - Willowbrook, IL April 2023 to Present

Running successful shifts, following up on training, creating daily plans for team members, ensuring proper quality is met throughout shift, handling guest opportunity responses, ordering, tracking sales and food cost, nightly reporting of sales and shortages, managing the activities of 40+ people on each shift at a high volume location. I am in charge of all ordering in the building. Ensuring orders are placed in a timely manner as well as accurately.

Assistant General Manager (AGM)

Buffalo Wild Wings - Morris, IL August 2022 to April 2023

I returned to buffalo wild wings as the AGM to assist the general manager in running the restaurant. My duties included entire FOH operations. Details of that include: scheduling, ordering, inventory control, profit and loss, hiring, interviewing, coaching and developing, managing safety and security, ensuring guest satisfaction, following up on operations and step of service, training, and ensuring safe alcohol service.

Restaurant Manager

Portillos Restaurant - Shorewood, IL October 2020 to August 2022

Running successful shifts, following up on training, creating daily plans for team members, ensuring proper quality is met throughout shift, handling guest opportunity responses, ordering, tracking sales and food cost, nightly reporting of sales and shortages, managing the activities of 40+ people on each shift at a high volume location.

Area Operations Manager

Dave And Busters - Orland Park, IL April 2018 to March 2021

Area operations manager of the bar department. Have worked for the company for over 2 years now. First was in charge of guest services department. Maintaining quality interactions and ensuring proper seating

were main focus in that are. Was in charge of hiring, training and providing schedules to all team members in this department. They added the role of winner circle manager In addition to guest services which meant I was also in charge of the prize area as well. Loss prevention, correct inventory, and Maintaining high efficiencies for that specific area of the business in addition to hiring, training and scheduling for those specific departments. Job duties also included warehouse management, checking in and confirming correct orders, maintaining organization, updating and reorganization, ensuring cleanliness and safety standards. As the main manager showing consistency in results and numbers, I was promoted to bar manager in October of 2019. Priorities in the bar we're ensuring alcohol sales were increasing, all bartenders were following strict drink count guidelines to ensure safe serving, all drinks were made to spec, carding every guest, cleanliness at its highest priority, And hospitality was at its highest for every guest. All other duties such as ensuring efficiencies, loss prevention, scheduling, hiring and training all remained the same but for this specific department.

Manager

Famous Dave's - Orland Park October 2017 to April 2018

I currently am in charge of front of house operations. This includes all server, bar and hospitality schedules. I am in charge of ensuring guest satisfaction levels stay above target and team member performance. I am also in charge of all hiring and training programs.

Assistant General Manager

Buffalo Wild Wings - Morris, IL February 2016 to October 2017

Started at Buffalo Wild Wings as a front of house manager. Was promoted to kitchen manager within 9 months. After my one year anniversary I was promoted to operations general manager. I was in charge of all operations of the restaurant and ensuring the quality of guest satisfaction was at its highest. Due to Buffalo Wild Wings changing their management tiers my title as operations general manager was adjusted to assistant general manager. I am in charge of all operations, including budgeting expenses, managing inventory, hiring, training, scheduling, pnl man-agement, ensuring all safety and company standards are being met each day, ensuring all audits are performed at a rating of exceeds expectations, training new shift managers, ensuring kitchen production is fast and efficient. I helped open the restaurant and during that process our profit after controlled expenses was well over 30%. We have maintained a customer experience score of 90% for the last year with the exception of one month. Our unannounced audit scores have maintained at or above 93%. And our labor budget has been met for the last 6 months straight.

Restaurant General Manager

Taco Bell - Minooka, IL September 2008 to February 2016

I started with this company as a team member and worked my way to restaurant general manager within a short period of time. I did this by being very focused on the job and tasks at hand. Current responsibilities include staffing, management training, supply orders and inventory control. Ensuring day to day operations and safety standards are met. Ensuring guest satisfaction. Scheduling and training plans. Consistently maintained high levels of cleanliness, organization, storage, and sanitation of food and beverage products to ensure quality.Performed restaurant walk-throughs to gauge timeliness and excellent service quality.

Cashier/Coffee Host

Pilot Travel Center - Minooka, IL August 2005 to May 2008

Responsibilities were cash handling, customer service, POS knowledge, general maintenance duties. I was in charge of food safety in the deli, restaurant organization, cleanliness. Basic working knowledge of CAT scales.

Cashier

Wal-Mart - Minooka, IL March 2004 to February 2005

Responsibilities include cash handling, POS knowledge, customer service, general area maintenance.

Education

General Education Degree

Joliet Junior College - Joliet, IL 2006

Skills

- Fast learner
- leadership skills (10+ years)
- · problem solving
- scheduling
- P&L Management
- · Profit & Loss
- Food Safety
- Restaurant Management
- Management
- Root cause analysis
- Kitchen Management Experience
- Loss Prevention
- Purchasing
- Forecasting
- Strategic Planning
- Budgeting
- · Guest Services
- Labor Cost Analysis
- Team Management
- Inventory Control
- Restaurant Experience

Certifications and Licenses

ServSafe Food Protection Manager

July 2022

Additional Information

Communication skills
Employee scheduling
Fast learner
Hard worker
P&L management
Complex problem solving
Strong leadership skills